Đặng Thị Duyên

MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

Objective

Being excellent staff with sophisticated knowledge about the job. Using all my affords and experiences to increase the company's turnover. Being confident and flexible in communication, taking all the opportunities to support my Medical Representative career.



Education

HA NOI UNIVERSITY OF PHARMACY

09/2013 - 06/2017

Major: Pharmaceutical

Degree: Good



Work Experience -

TRONG TIN PHARMACY

03/2010-12/2011

Saler in Pharmacy

- Providing advice about health issues, symptoms and medications in response to customer enquiries.
- Ordering and selling medicines.

THACOPHAR COMPANY

01/2012-08/2013

Saler in Hapulico Market

- Introducing new products for the customers.
- Ordering and selling medicines.

THUAN GIA COMPANY

08/2016-11/2017

Medical Representative (OTC)

- Business development in the pharmacy channel in the assigned territory.
- Building strong rapport, creating and maintaining good relationship with targeted customers.
- Keep up-to-date product knowledge.
- Feedback competitors' activities.

OLLIN COMPANY (DANONE NUTRICIA)

11/2017 - PRESENT

Medical Representative (ETC)

- Organising appointments and meetings with healthcare staff.
- Demonstrating or presenting products to healthcare staff including doctors, nurses and pharmacists.
- Attending and organising trade exhibitions, conferences and meetings.
- writing reports and other documents.

Personal Quality _

Sense of responsibility and carefulness.



- ☐ April, 20, 1988
- ☐ Female
- 0986903107
- □ dangtduyen88@gmail.com
- Hanoi, Vietnam
- https://www.facebook.com/duyen.dang.902

SKILLS

Computer

Logical thinking and creative

Teamwork

Communication

INTERESTS

- Music
- football
- Reading book

Hard working and ready to face new challenges.
Friendly and adaptable in communication.